You're watching Chef & My Fridge,
the sibling special.
BIBI and NaKyoung,
the Gyeongsang-do sisters,
and Jonathan and Patricia,
the Jeolla-do siblings, are here with us.
Jonathan and Patricia
must be the hottest siblings
in the entertainment industry.
One of our chefs said
they've been benchmarking Jonathan's wit.
-Benchmarking?
-Yes.
-It's Jong-won.
-Really?
-Yes.
-How so?
When it comes to this show, I believe I am
the rising comedian.
-He really wants to be funny.
-He does.
I've been working as hard on my jokes
as I do my culinary career.
HIS FAN IS MOVED
-He's trying quite hard.
-I think
-you are quite unrivaled.
-I am?
You have a distinct color.
COLOR?
-Wait, "distinct color"?
-We do have a color, yes.
Everybody has a color.
EMERGENCY
EVERYTHING HAPPENED IN JUST 3 SECONDS
You have to patch this up.
The direction.
I mean, we all have color.
SO WHICH COLOR IS IT?
SOMEONE, JUST CLEAR MY THOUGHTS
You mean he has a distinct wit.
Yes, he has his own color.
Will you stop using the word, "color"?
He has his personality.
-Say that he's set apart.
-Right.
I watched his video titled
"Culinary Cook Wars," and it was so funny.
-"Culinary Cook Wars"?
-I did a parody
of Culinary Class Wars
on my own channel.
He's the white spoon?
I literally did it black and white.
WHO WAS THE WHITE SPOON?
I invited a Caucasian friend.
ACTUAL BLACK AND WHITE SPOONS
That's what you call black comedy.
HEY!
That's a no-no.
It wasn't just black and white spoons.
There was an Asian spoon too.
-Right.
-Yes, he was there.
It showed the harmony
between three different races.
Many people enjoyed it very much.
-Jonathan said this.
-Yes?
"I'm much less funny
when I'm on shows with Patricia."
WHY?
-Really?
-I thought you two were funny.
-You two are funny.
-Is that so?
When I'm on variety shows,
I think a bit of exaggeration
is always necessary.
We need that MSG.
That's true.
Let's say
I usually eat three bowls of rice.
I could always say five on a show.
-Right.
-Yes.
-True.
-I eat a lot, period.
Although no one cared about me at school,
I could always just say,
"I was a popular kid."
But she keeps correcting it.
PATRICIA POINTS OUT THE EXAGGERATIONS
She goes, "That's not true.
You only eat two bowls."
She corrects you.
And she makes the show so dry.
MY SIS MAKES THE SHOW DRY
-But it should be juicy.
-We want that juice.
She makes it so dry.
She's like a dryer.
VARIETY SHOW DRYER
-She's a dryer.
-She is.
It's tough to do my job.
Other people run with your story
knowing that it's exaggerated.
I think variety shows
are all about sincerity and honesty.
-That's also true.
-That's my take.
If he gets caught exaggerating,
-it can blow up.
-Yes.
-How will you patch it up?
-That's true.
Yet you change your voice on TV?
VOICE CHANGE?
This isn't her usual voice.
-What's it like?
-Much deeper, like a rapper.
-"Hi, I'm Patricia."
-Really?
-She changes on TV.
-No.
-Is it an exaggeration?
-No way.
-Is this your TV voice?
THE BROTHER'S HAVING FUN
-Give us your real voice.
-Do it.
-Say, "Come and eat."
-Patricia.
Come and eat.
It's still fake.
-"Come and eat."
-During the break,
-…I'll try to record her real voice.
-Yes, record it.
-Record it.
Even as we expose each other like this,
when one of us does this, we have to stop.
-It's a stop sign.
-It's a sign?
Hey, we should do that too.
USES IT IMMEDIATELY
-You'd better stop.
-It's a sign.
-We have to stop there.
-It's a good idea.
-The higher it rises…
-This means it's really bad.
-The higher?
-They're good.
Chefs, if you hear something
you don't want to talk about, do this.
PLEASE STOP ATTACKING ME
It's a good idea.
-We'll do this when you aren't funny.
-Okay.
NERVOUS
Take a good look at me.
When I'm like this,
it means you weren't funny.
If your story
is highly likely to be edited out…
NERVOUS
THANK YOU FOR SHARING
THE AWESOME SIBLING CULTURE
Do you two really have
an awful relationship?
You aren't following
each other's social media accounts.
-Really?
-They aren't?
I've been curious too.
Isn't this the norm?
Families usually don't do that.
-Do you?
-Really?
Like my wife and I.
-Wait, you should do that.
-Really?
-Can you tell us why?
-What's going on there?
Well, I follow her,
but my wife won't follow me back.
She even made it private.
You don't do it between family.
-You could feel conscious about it.
-Yes.
I never followed him from the start,
but I think there are spies
among my followers.
Whenever I upload something,
within an hour, he says,
"Patricia, that's too short.
Patricia, lower that shirt."
-Screening.
-He's censoring her.
-He's keeping tabs on her.
-You don't even follow each other.
I usually let it pass,
but sometimes,
she wears something too tribal.
Something way too short, you know.
-Like she came from the Neolithic Age.
-The Paleolithic Age.
PLEASE STOP
I wonder, "Is she going hunting?"
Going hunting?
To collect and catch food?
-Oh, no.
-Like a mammoth?
-Yes, I wonder if she's hunting a mammoth.
-Stop it.
Those pictures are hard to let pass.
-It's now.
-The sign.
I'll tone it down 2%.
But it was funny. Keep going.
OPEN UP
-He's opening up.
-It was funny.
-I'm up to here.
-So funny.
Jonathan also said this.
"The worst comment I have ever seen
was someone saying we look alike."
-I mean, you're siblings.
-It's natural.
But we don't.
We aren't alike.
-You aren't.
-No.
We really aren't.
We're just similarly colored. That's all.
MUST FEEL QUITE WRONGED
His eyes are kind of glazed.
He always goes around looking like this.
-Like this. They're unfocused.
-That's true.
JUDGES HIM READILY
I'm doing my best now.
I'd go, "Are you asleep?"
Patricia has sparkly eyes, though.
-Her eyes are different.
-Yes, our eyes are so different.
-Our eyes are already different.
-Right.
What if he put on lashes?
-Yes.
-That's true.
Whenever I put on wigs,
I get some awful comments
asking if Patricia has come.
-Awful comments?
-I get DMs too.
-"I saw you at the shoot today."
-Yes, that they saw her.
We'd like to ask our viewers,
so can you two get closer?
-Like this?
-Yes, get closer. Closer.
-Are we getting paid extra for this?
-Right?
OH, YES, THE TOUCHING RATE SHEET
You can get 50,000 won more each.
-Okay, 50,000 won.
-I see. 50,000 won.
Add hands for 30,000 won more.
-No.
WE CAN'T GIVE YOU MORE EITHER
The siblings may bicker like this,
but in reality,
Jonathan adores his little sister so much.
ME?
He bought a car for Patricia.
-Which model?
-He's an awesome older brother.
-Really?
-That's not an easy decision.
It might sound like he's a great brother.
But the monthly payment is on me.
Wait.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
-It wasn't paid in full?
-It wasn't, and I'm making the payments.
A NEW PARADIGM FOR A PRESENT
Is it truly a gift?
It is. Think about it.
I really don't want to see her get lazy.
What is he talking about?
THE ELDEST CAN RELATE
I didn't pay it off entirely.
I don't want to spoil her.
How many months did you pay off?
I can't disclose that.
THAT'S PRIVATE INFORMATION…
Will people come for you?
He'll have to leave.
Is she paying off the entire thing?
-He just went and signed the papers.
-What is this?
JONATHAN'S PRESENT: SIGNATURE
What's going on
between you and the dealer?
-Is he a friend?
-Right?
-He got a kickback, 100%.
-Yes, he got a kickback.
-He got a kickback.
-I think so.
DOESN'T DENY IT
-A kickback of 100 million won.
-Wait.
Jonathan lives in Seoul,
and Patricia still lives in Gwangju.
-You don't live together?
-No.
I slept at a hotel last night.
He got a room for me.
How nice.
-Why not your place?
-Why did you do that?
He… Well, this is yet another long story.
He hates it when I stay at his place.
He moved two months ago,
and he claimed that
he hadn't unpacked everything yet.
-After two months?
-Two months?
I'm wondering
if he's unpacking one article a day.
-She can always come and help.
-Yes.
It's not helping.
DOING WHATEVER IT TAKES TO KEEP HER OUT
We have different routines. For example,
I love to work out,
so I always have to do cardio
before I eat.
But she's not like that.
She only likes to eat.
-So we aren't on the same page.
-You aren't.
I've tried before
and thought we could work out together,
so I even got her a gym membership.
But she never went,
so I paid them for nothing.
-It happens.
-Patricia likes
to donate to many different gyms.
A CHARITABLE FIGURE IN THE GYM INDUSTRY
She'd only keep weighing herself.
Just the weighing machine.
-The machines are different.
-She needs the information.
The gyms in the neighborhood
all share her physical information.
You've never been to his new place?
Once.
But he only let me in at that time
because I came with my mom.
I'll invite her once I'm done cleaning.
I'm done with the bedroom now.
-Now?
-Yes.
Are you there alone?
Of course.
TREMBLING
DOES HE HAVE MORE TO CLEAN UP?
Is it time for this?
If you're thirsty, you can have mine too.
Of course, I'm alone.
These siblings are so funny,
so I expect to see
something fun in the fridge too.
It's time to go through
Jonathan and Patricia's fridge.
But you don't live together.
-No.
-No, so the fridge's mine.
I don't have to see his fridge
to know that he doesn't have much.
He also doesn't cook,
so I stocked it up a bit.
-Because she has to eat too.
-Yes.
-That's important.
-She can't miss out.
-She's here to eat.
-Of course.
Let's see it, then.
Jonathan and Patricia's fridge.
He really doesn't have much.
What's going to happen?
I'm so excited.
-Don't be.
-It's empty.
We present Jonathan and Patricia's fridge!
It's practically empty.
-What is this?
-What's going on?
-Fridge!
-It's practically empty.
EMPTY
This doesn't look promising.
It's so empty.
Nothing's in there.
AWKWARD…
-It looks like trouble.
-Hey.
Do you see that full shelf?
-Here?
-That's my doing.
-Those are Patricia's.
-Yes.
If I didn't do that,
we would've just eaten some cereal.
We'd eat cereal, and that'd be it.
Let's see.
The top shelf has only beverages.
You have a whole lot of these.
I love the feeling
of gulping down something cold.
-He's into beverages.
-When I set
my mind on having
a particular beverage that month,
I like to buy it in bulk
and drink it at home.
It's just one type.
Yes, I only drink one type.
I only go after one thing.
-Once you get hooked?
-Yes.
The second shelf has sweet potato mousse.
-That's so good.
-You have two bags…
-That one.
-…of the mousse.
My all-time favorite late-night snack
is SCP, sweet potato and cheese
pork cutlet.
SCP.
-I love sweet potatoes and cheese.
-SCP is good.
But whenever I order some,
they don't give me
as much mousse as I want.
HE'S LEFT WANTING MORE
-That's why.
-It's not enough.
So I got that bag
to cover the dish with the mousse,
-then eat it.
-You can't even see the cutlets.
HAPPINESS♥
Sounds good.
And even on pizza.
I order a cheese pizza and…
All over the top.
But you get some on the crust.
-It's not enough.
-It's not.
Do you both like it?
-We do.
-We both like it.
This one.
-It sounds good.
-You two seemed so friendly right now.
I was just happy.
-We're on the same page.
-Food united them.
-You looked so happy.
-They're like each other.
-After all, we're siblings.
-We are.
DEFINITELY THE SAME BLOOD
-This family loves spicy food too.
-Yes.
-Cheongyang pepper.
-Cheongyang pepper and the powder.
They also had Cheongyang pepper
and bird's eye chili in the last episode.
Those are spicy.
How much spiciness can you take?
-Well…
You've probably heard of that dish,
Deadly Pork Cutlet.
I KNOW
I can eat everything other than that.
-Have you had it?
-Have you?
I almost died.
JUST LIKE ITS NAME…
It was so crazy.
TOO SPICY TO IMAGINE
Was that too spicy for you?
I can handle pretty much anything
if it's deliciously spicy.
If it's something like Buldak sauce,
I'd sprinkle it everywhere.
Whenever I got thirsty,
I'd just chug it too.
-You did that?
-What?
An exaggeration.
Was anything he said exaggerated?
-No, not yet.
-Not yet?
And in my case,
when I order spicy tteokbokki,
I never go below the original spiciness.
Us too.
I've been eating
the milder version lately.
-BIBI's grown weaker.
-You have.
-She's weaker.
-I've been on the decline.
Indigestion came with age.
Are you the eldest among the four?
-Yes.
-That's it. You're on the decline.
So I have to eat more now.
Yes, you end up compromising.
-It's sad to think about.
-It is?
Our chefs have work ethics,
so they won't make it overly spicy.
-Oh…
-It can be bad for you.
-Please cross the line today.
-Way over the line.
-Over the line?
-Whoa.
What's this one?
Toast? It says it's for toasts.
That's not easy to find.
-What is it?
-I am seriously
in love with I toast franchise.
-Yes, that sauce was a big deal.
-That's right.
-I know.
-One day,
I went to an event
and saw them doing a pop-up store.
I began to lurk around, and…
-He kept lurking, so they said, "Take it."
-They gave me some.
PRECIOUS SAUCE HE BEGGED FOR
I've been trying my best
not to overeat it.
That's like caviar to me.
-It feels like that?
-Yes, caviar.
I only spread a bit when I eat my toast.
JUST ADDING A BIT OF THE SCENT
What if Patricia eats it all?
-That'll be her last day on earth.
-Wait.
-It'll be the second punch.
-My face will become symmetrical, then.
He's trying to make this last.
Can the chefs use this?
Oh, what?
As an ingredient.
-He's pretending not to hear it.
-No?
Is this the only thing you can use?
What you have is what we can use.
This is it, of course.
Yes, right.
Please use just a little, then.
-Try to save it.
-Try to save it, please.
If he doesn't like the dish
you made with this, it'll be trouble.
-Please be wise.
-Please do that.
-He has apple jam too.
-Peanut butter and apple jam.
I love bread,
especially baguettes.
So I love to visit a bakery
around 7 to 8 a.m.,
because I can find freshly baked bread.
I'd take the warm bread and break it.
Then I spread
some peanut butter on it and eat it.
-I see.
-That sounds so delicious.
So you like both sweet and spicy food.
I like something that's primal.
"Primal"?
Something that's true
to the human instinct.
Sweet, salty, and spicy. That's it.
How about Pyongyang-style naengmyeon?
It was such a huge shock.
It was just water and noodles.
IT TASTED TOO BLAND FOR HIM
-Like boiled water.
-I never went back.
You too, Patricia?
We do have a similar appetite,
but he's worse than me.
He has a serious case of a sweet tooth.
So he eats twisted donuts covered in sugar
topped with peanut butter,
along with milk tea.
People usually eat sweet things
with non-sweet drinks,
-like milk, right?
-Right?
-But he likes everything sweet.
-Everything.
The milk tea is made with low-fat milk.
He calls it low-fat,
but he adds sugar to it.
-I wondered why.
-Why even bother with low-fat milk?
-Like six spoons.
-Low-fat, high-sugar.
He's not doing a low-sugar diet.
I like my food with a bit of sweetness.
I even add sugar to watermelon.
-Really? Watermelon is already sweet.
-One more thing.
When I eat jeon,
I add some sugar there too.
-What?
-To jeon?
Try adding some to potato jeon.
-Potato jeon?
-He asked us to try it.
Potato jeon with sugar is so good.
-It sounds good.
-It is.
-It does.
-It's really good.
Well, sometimes we dip
boiled potatoes in sugar.
That's it.
How come no one does that with jeon?
He has a point.
-It's a new paradigm.
-It's unfair.
SUGGESTING POTATO JEON WITH SUGAR
-What's that?
-That's kimchi.
-From your home?
-Tae-won's mom usually sends me some.
-Who?
-Tae-won.
My high school friend.
NAME-DROPPING HIS FRIEND
I thought
you were talking about Kim Tae-won.
No, not him.
-Tae-won?
-Who's Tae-won?
-He's my friend from high school.
-High school friend?
His mother always sends me kimchi
because I love what she made.
But she couldn't send me some
since I recently moved.
So that's store-bought.
-So it's not from Tae-won's mom?
-No.
She'll probably send me some
after watching this.
I think it's time, ma'am.
ARE YOU WATCHING THIS, TAE-WON'S MOM?
So is Tae-won doing well?
-He is.
-Great.
He recently got a job.
And some fruits.
When do you eat your fruit?
Patricia and I like to dip fruit in salt.
SALT?
-It's good.
-Orange and salt tastes so good.
Orange and salt?
Salt? Why do you dip it in salt?
Your mouth explodes with water.
It hits you right here.
That zing?
That zapping feeling?
-Every liquid in your body comes out.
-A hit of dopamine.
When you eat lemon and salt
after chugging a shot of tequila,
-it hits you hard.
-Yes.
-It does.
-It must be like that.
They have
such a different way of eating things.
-I feel so happy when I eat.
-These siblings are something.
-Let's take a look at Patricia's shelf.
-My shelf.
-Carrots.
-It's not enough.
-Sweet potato.
And some meat.
-Beef, chicken, and pork.
-Chicken and pork.
Yes, I open my mornings with meat.
-You do?
-I start my day with protein.
How do you eat it?
Pork belly, rice, and chili peppers.
-In the morning?
-It sounds good.
-What are these? Avocados?
-Avocados.
I really love avocados.
-I see.
-Avocados.
I take warm bread
and spread avocado like jam
and just eat it.
-Just the avocado.
Jonathan isn't too excited.
You don't like it, do you?
-I'm not into it.
-He's not.
It was really great because
I was the only one eating them
even when we lived together.
-It's great.
-It must've been.
What's the best dish you can make?
I love spicy braised chicken,
so I often make it myself.
-Really?
-Most people make it
with potatoes, but I like
to switch it out with sweet potatoes.
WOW
-I do that.
-Have you had it?
-Yes.
-I had to. She always makes a huge batch.
She makes enough to last for a few days.
I can live off it for a week or two.
Then do you only eat that
during that time?
There were days
when I had to eat out because of that.
What's this?
Yuja cheong and ginger cheong.
My favorites are misugaru, grain drink,
ginger cheong, and yuja cheong.
So I love this yuja soda right now.
He'll order this in bulk too.
-I would.
-It'll be my drink for next month.
Thanks so much.
They help out a lot with our production.
-It's great that you pointed it out.
-It is.
-I love yuja so much.
-That's Jonathan.
It's perfect.
LET'S ALL HAVE A SIP WHILE WE'RE AT IT♥
-Namhae is famous for yuja.
-It is.
-We're so grateful for this.
-Let's look at the freezer.
Beef belly jjamppong.
Do you enjoy jjamppong?
I do. I like how spicy it is.
I like to order fried rice
at Chinese places,
hoping that it'll be served
with a side of jjamppong soup.
-But some places don't do that.
-Right.
-Egg soup?
-Yes, it's egg soup.
-That's so disappointing to me.
-Of course.
I'm like, "It's over."
But egg soup is more traditional.
I'd have to order a bowl of jjamppong too.
-I get you.
-Right?
You have thinly sliced pork belly.
-Yes, we both like it.
-We like it.
It's summer now, and it's really good
when served with some spicy noodles.
It's to die for.
Literally.
I love that expression.
"It's to die for."
"Die."
Seasoned boneless chicken?
-Fried chicken.
-I get those instead of ordering chicken.
Really?
That changed my paradigm
of fried chicken. It's so good.
-I'll have to try those.
-Is it good?
Top kimchi fried rice with that chicken,
and a piece
of Tae-won's mom's kimchi. Yum.
-Salty, salty, salty.
-It kills you too?
-Salty, salty, and salty.
Everything is salty.
You two have great chemistry.
-Let's make peace. Seriously.
-Only when it comes to food.
You two might even hug.
It might be possible.
That was Jonathan and Patricia's fridge,
full of primal flavors.
FINISHED CHECKING OUT
JONATHAN AND PATRICIA'S FRIDGE
It's time to share
the siblings' order.
Show us.
-So Sweet That It's to Die for.
-Sweet?
So Spicy That It's to Die for.
Are you trying to say goodbye to her?
One of us has to go.
-One of you?
-Yes, one of us has to go.
-Are you trying to get rid of her?
-No.
That's not it.
The first round is a sweet dish.
Yes, I picked the sweet round.
I love sweet things so much
because it's so instinctive.
And think about what humans say
when they're exhausted.
-I need sugar.
-"I'm low on sugar."
Exactly.
That's how important sweetness is.
Are they correlated?
So feel free to step over the line
and make me something sweet.
"Step over the line." You're allowed to
make Patricia unconscious.
-Right?
-Yes.
Are you just looking for a dish
that'll take Patricia down?
No, but that's a plus.
2 BIRDS, 1 STONE
A primal flavor.
-Primal sweetness.
-All right.
So Patricia chose
So Spicy That It's to Die for?
I really love spicy food,
but we've never had anything spicy enough
that would satisfy our appetite.
NOT EVEN BIRD'S EYE CHILI
So please try to satisfy us.
Something that can kill Jonathan?
Yes, so that he can't even get in the car.
Make him stay in the restroom.
They're trying to end each other.
WHO'LL END UP SURVIVING?
Four of you remain at the moment.
Poong, Sam, Sung-jun, and Nam-no.
-Me!
-Sung-jun?
I'm quite good at making desserts.
WOW♥
So the sweet round.
SO SWEET THAT IT'S TO DIE FOR
Dessert.
Sung-jun takes the first slot.
-Who's next?
-I'll go.
-Whoa.
-Nam-no.
Sweet or spicy?
-Sweet.
-Sweetness.
Sung-jun has been too smug lately.
Yes, you need to teach him a lesson.
They're sitting here together
with similar hairstyle and size.
But they're different
like an otter and a sea otter.
Otter and sea otter?
-He looks more sharp.
-She's right on.
He'd go, "Huh?"
even after losing his clams.
PERFECT CHARACTER ANALYSIS
All right. He takes the sweet round.
Then it's automatic.
Poong and Sam have to make spicy dishes.
-Is it okay, Sam?
-Is it all right?
It's a huge challenge.
THE NATURALIST CHEF'S CHALLENGE
-I'm so bad with spicy food.
-Sam is a guy…
-…who never drops his work ethic.
-Never.
But he has to do that today.
-He'll have to try.
-I'll do my best.
Please call 911 first.
EXCITED
-Have them on standby.
-Oh, my.
I'll make it that spicy.
THE AUTHORITY ON SPICY FOOD
-Call 911? We might be carried away.
-Call 911?
-We'll eat on the ambulance.
-All right, then.
Let us begin the sweetness round
between Chef Kwon Sung-jun
and Chef Yoon Nam-no!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
The first cook-off with ingredients
from Jonathan and Patricia's fridge.
-It's a battle between the Tubby Twins.
-Tubby twins.
You're not it?
Chef Kwon Sung-jun, Nam-no's look-alike,
versus Chef Yoon Nam-no,
Sung-jun's look-alike.
He went on a diet
and lost a lot of weight
not to get called that.
But people still say you two are similar.
-He looks disturbed.
-You don't look pleased.
Earlier today,
BIBI said something.
You're bringing that up?
Why did he enunciate my name? "BIBI."
-"BIBI."
-BIBI said
that we look quite alike.
-She did.
-Their sizes.
And the image.
I was quite hurt.
We may look alike,
but I'm no longer tubby.
When it comes to BMI,
it's within the average range.
-BMI?
-You have to go there?
But I believe Chef Nam-no
is nicknamed 100 Nam-no.
His weight?
Don't bring up my weight.
He weighs 0.1 tons.
-So we're no longer on the same level.
-You aren't tubby now.
I find his statement quite unpleasant.
If he were a lottery ticket,
he'd be a losing one
that's not even worth 500 won.
He still looks the same.
He hasn't changed much?
These disses are intense.
He lost weight,
but his looks remained the same.
Even in the green room,
he kept looking in the mirror,
wondering if he's better looking.
He looks at the mirror often?
-It's rough.
-That gesture is awful too.
WOBBLING
-He's an eyesore.
-Him?
Yes, it's detestable.
SO UNFAIR…
He doesn't just look in the mirror.
He tries to make his eyelids
double and even triple.
APPALLED
You can triple them?
Before, his features were tiny,
while the background was wide.
But he had lost some sujebi
and reduced the background.
Compared to the entire background,
his features are still not big enough.
He did get rid of sujebi,
but he's an Italian chef,
so he has some gnocchi on the side.
-Gnocchi is so good.
-It's delicious.
Two chefs are out there,
but we're only talking about Sung-jun.
VERY PLEASED
He's happy about it.
He's thrilled.
Sung-jun the attention lover.
They have an interesting dynamic.
They've fought four times last year,
and Nam-no has won all four times.
This year, they've fought twice,
and Sung-jun has won both rounds.
WON BOTH ROUNDS
It was about time Nam-no showed
what he did last year and beat him.
Chef Sung-jun is the type
who likes
to think his way through cooking.
He's good at grasping the order,
-and he often says fancy words…
-The analyst.
-to entice guests.
-He's an analyst.
I may not be as good
at deciphering the order,
but I do cook a dish that suits the order.
-What do you mean?
-He found the conclusion by himself.
He didn't get a grasp of the order,
but he cooked a dish
according to his understanding.
That's why you're slow.
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
He's trying to say
that Sung-jun plays dirty.
-You wanted to say that.
-Yes, a bit.
-I want to say something to him.
-Sure.
Sung-jun, your hair…
Wait, not the hair.
Sung-jun, you don't cook by thinking.
You taste it.
It's your tongue.
"Your tongue"?
-It doesn't sound good.
-That was weird.
-What's he saying?
-It sounds like you've heard some quotes,
-but it didn't mix.
-He didn't remember them right.
At first, he almost said,
"Sung-jun, your hair is made of cooking."
I can't believe you got that wrong.
Go home and read a little.
I do, actually.
He seems confident about this.
You were an ant in the previous life?
-What does he mean?
-An ant?
I have a serious case of a sweet tooth.
-Right.
-Ants love sweet stuff.
-That's true.
Don't people usually go with bees?
OH, RIGHT
He probably gained
most of his weight because of sweets.
-I'm a pig now, but I was an ant.
-Sure.
Many don't know,
but even among ants,
-termites are rather tubby.
-Sure.
Sorry.
MAKES THE SIGN
Do the sign.
EVERYONE PRAYS
PLEASE STOP NOW, GRANDPA
KIDDOS…
CHEF SUNG-JUN'S INGREDIENTS:
BONELESS CHICKEN THIGHS, MILK
SWEET POTATO MOUSSE, CHEESE SLICES,
PEANUT BUTTER, YUJA CHEONG, AND MORE
What I'm making today is
It's Been O-range Since Nam-no Won a Star.
TRIGGERED…
Are you using orange?
-That was a good one.
-O-range.
I thought Chef Nam-no would make
a simple, ordinary dessert
because it's a dessert round.
GASP…
So I'll serve dessert and the main dish,
two different dishes.
I'm making orange chicken.
-Orange chicken?
-It sounds good.
-It's eaten in America and Southeast Asia.
American Chinese.
I'll mix it with peanut butter,
which he likes,
then make quick fried rice
and top it with chicken.
I'll prepare that simple dish.
As for the dessert, I'll make choux batter
-and fill it up…
-Choux?
…like your favorite pork cutlets.
-Wow.
-I'll use sweet potato mousse
and even cheese,
then fry it like churros.
-Wow.
-This is insane.
-I've decided.
-You have?
-I have.
-Sung-jun wins?
-Do I push it now?
-Listen.
-Hear out Nam-no too.
-There's Chef Nam-no.
There's one more.
-More?
-Three dishes?
I'll finish it off
with a coat
of Jonathan's favorite toast sauce.
HAND ON THE FOREHEAD IN UNISON
Can he win against this?
Can you resist my dishes?
You told them not to use too much.
He can use a little bit.
-Just moderately.
-No, please use it.
-It's not your sauce.
-Well, no.
SENSITIVE WITH THE SAUCE
-"It's not your sauce."
-Just a little bit.
CHEF NAM-NO'S INGREDIENTS:
BANANA, SWEET POTATO MOUSSE, MILK
PEAR, YUJA CHEONG, APPLE JAM,
ORANGE, BREAD, CEREAL, GRAPEFRUIT CHEONG
Chef Nam-no is up against him today.
What are you making?
Good luck with your tongue.
-I shall blab with my tongue.
-Blab on.
My dish is called
Beat Sung-jun Brûlée.
-Whoa.
-Beat Sung-jun Brûlée?
-Beat Sung-jun Brûlée.
BEAT SUNG-JUN BRÛLÉE
-Are you making brûlée?
So you're just making a dessert,
and that's it?
I'm just making a dessert.
He was right.
He's making a few dishes.
-You shouldn't say it like that.
-He's making a few.
He's this predictable?
-Deny it.
-My gosh.
I'm making two desserts, actually.
For one,
I'll use your favorite ingredient,
-sweet potato mousse…
-Sweet potato.
…and banana to make crème brûlée.
-Wow.
-That's the first one.
The second one is a dish
which Poong had failed to make,
the reversed kouign-amann.
But today, I'll make
a proper-looking one.
-Kouign-amann?
You said you loved sweets.
I want something so sweet
that knocks me out after a bite.
-I want to faint.
-Yes.
I'll see if you can do that.
I'll make it so sweet that
you'll get cavities when you touch it.
Isn't that a bad thing?
You might need a dentist's appointment.
-I should make it right away.
-Yes.
You'll get a good blood sugar spike.
And now, let us begin the round,
"So Sweet That It's to Die for."
-Let's go!
-I'm so excited.
I kind of want to win today.
-You can.
-You got this.
-You can do it.
-Good luck.
"My body has been built on sugar."
The show's ant, Chef Yoon Nam-no.
"Nam-no is my prey today."
The show's anteater, Chef Kwon Sung-jun.
That suits him.
He should go and lick him.
A battle so fierce that it's to die for!
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
THE SWEET TOOTH ROUND BEGINS
They're making sweet dishes.
I'm sure we'll see a lot of sugar be used.
STARTING WITH A PILE OF SUGAR
-I love that first move.
-You do?
He added a huge pile.
Is that so?
He likes that move, Nam-no.
A BUCKET OF SUGAR
Nam-no starts off
by taking most of the attention.
MAKING THE CHICKEN
TO GO WITH THE FRIED RICE
Is that chicken, Sung-jun?
-It's chicken.
-He's cooking with chicken.
Chicken, my favorite.
-Orange chicken.
-Yes.
I think he's already done.
He's deep-frying the chicken.
It's more Japanese-style
than Korean-style fried chicken.
Yes, that batter's Japanese-style.
Is the heat high enough?
-I want to cook it slowly over low heat.
-That is Japanese-style.
-So it doesn't sizzle?
-No.
He said he'd make brûlée with a banana.
What will he do? He's hollowing it out.
He's hollowing out a banana.
Chef Nam-no
tends to look smart when he cooks quietly.
Sweet potato.
-Wow. The mousse.
-The sweet potato mousse.
Seriously?
-That's something you add everywhere.
-Yes.
-You said it was never enough.
-Right.
He's squeezing it out.
INTO HIS MOUTH AS WELL
Banana and sweet potato?
Do they go well together?
1. MAKE SWEET MOUSSE
Sweet potato mousse.
FINISHED BANANA SWEET POTATO MOUSSE
-What's that?
-A pear.
-That looks good.
-Look.
-He's slicing it thinly.
-He is.
-It looks so pretty.
-I love pears too.
He really has a sweet tooth.
-Jonathan is mostly looking at Nam-no.
-What?
-He gets my attention.
-Right?
THE OLDER TUBBY TWIN IS ON A ROLL
Why do you need so much pear?
YUMMY
Wait, is it for himself?
He keeps eating it.
-The fridge owners seem concerned.
-Oh, come on.
We have to taste and see
if a dish is seasoned well.
But it's true
that he tends to take bigger bites.
Even when he added the mousse,
he squeezed out this much and tasted it.
-We saw it all.
-He's having a meal.
-What's that yellow thing?
-Yuja cheong and apple jam.
Yuja cheong and apple jam.
-It sounds fruity.
-It sounds good.
MAKING THE CHOUX DOUGH
He's adding butter and flour.
Chef Sung-jun's making the choux dough.
-Choux dough?
So you're supposed to cook the batter
to make the dough.
That's it. How will he deep-fry that?
Can he deep-fry the choux dough?
-By squeezing it out like churros.
-Squeezing.
Now, add an egg and whisk!
He has to whisk it quickly.
Otherwise, the egg hardens.
It would harden.
He'll now add that to a piping bag.
What?
-Will he roll it out?
-The dough?
-He's spreading it out.
-It's not a piping bag.
-How will he deep-fry that?
-Exactly.
-Is there a way?
-I'm curious.
Is he going to deep-fry the whole thing?
Correct.
If he deep-fries that whole,
the dough will rise.
-It can look like bread.
-Really?
He rolled the choux dough
with sweet potato mousse and cheese.
Oh, he rolled it up?
He's now deep-frying the choux.
-Just like that?
-Sung-jun fries his choux.
Four minutes have passed.
-Already?
-Yes.
Only ten minutes left.
-Nam-no didn't throw away the peel.
-The banana peel?
He's stuffing it.
-That one looks sweet.
-It is.
It's like a dish
at a fine dining restaurant.
What's he putting on top?
-Sweet potato mousse.
-I love that.
You have to cover it up like that.
-It looks like a banana.
-It does.
-It became a banana again.
That's very creative, Nam-no.
He's sprinkling salt too.
-Sugar.
-It's sugar.
-There's no place for salt in this round.
-No salt.
Only sugar.
TORCH ON
He's scorching it like a crème brûlée.
-That banana looks intriguing.
-It looks good.
-That'll look pretty.
-Nam-no got creative.
-He keeps sprinkling more sugar.
-He's using a torch now.
It looks like a ripe banana.
That kid is quite smart.
-Yes, but why doesn't he have stars?
-Right?
TODAY, HE'S A SMART ONE
He added some salt too.
Salty and sweet is always nice.
Orange.
And orange zest.
-That looks so good.
-Doesn't it?
Sung-jun makes sauce.
ADD PEANUT BUTTER
Peanut butter.
Wait, soy sauce?
Dropping green onion.
YUJA CHEONG X 2
Orange.
He's juicing oranges.
It's Been O-range Since Nam-no Won a Star.
ADD TO THE CHICKEN SAUCE
-He added orange juice. And chicken?
-He added orange.
It's American Chinese food.
Yes, there's orange chicken,
but I've never seen it with peanut butter.
I see.
That's cool. It's all about creativity.
Sugar began to boil.
Something smells sweet.
-Butter.
-He's adding butter.
It'll turn into caramel.
WHOA
That's caramel?
BREAD FOR KOUIGN-AMANN
He's cutting that piece of bread.
He'll probably roll it back up.
He's going to roll it up?
He's making the shape.
BREAKS
I think it broke. It did!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
DISPOSED
OH NO
-Wet the bread.
-Flatten it with a rolling pin.
-Flatten it.
-It's okay.
HE BEGINS TO ROLL IT AGAIN
-Again?
-Is it okay? Don't let it break again.
SUCCESSFULLY ROLLED
He puts them on a stick.
What's his plan?
He made them like lollipops.
-That's just toasted bread.
-Right?
MURMURING…
-It's crouton.
-He'll do something.
Why are they suspicious of Nam-no?
-They're like hyenas.
-They are.
Five minutes, twenty seconds.
Is the choux ready?
Has it been fried well?
-That looks good.
-So that's what happens.
-That's amazing.
-It's ready.
It's probably soft inside, right?
-Probably.
-Right?
ANTICIPATION
Sung-ju, please report from the kitchen.
-Five minutes.
-Not much time left.
-What now?
-I'm on my way.
He's grabbing the fried chicken
and throwing them into the sauce.
-The chicken sauce.
-Orange sauce?
It's orange sauce.
-He juiced an orange into that.
-He did.
This is so new.
A NEW WORLD OF CHOUX
-It's burnt.
-It is?
-This choux looks burnt.
Isn't it burnt?
-Isn't it?
-No, it's not burnt.
It reminds me of sweet potato, actually.
One says it's burnt,
another says it's not.
HOW DID THE S-C CHOUX TURN OUT?
-It looks burnt.
-He got it out.
GRABBING CEREAL
Hey! Cereal.
GROUND AND READY TO GO
BREAD JUMPS INTO CARAMEL
…TURNING
-It would've been easier with two sticks.
-Yes, with two sticks.
But he couldn't think that far ahead.
-This bread…
-It looks good.
-…is topped with something.
-So good.
AMAZED
What did you coat it with?
BREAD COATED WITH CEREAL
That can't taste bad.
DELICIOUSLY THICK
With that much sugar?
COATED WITH CEREAL
KOUIGN-AMANN FOR BLOOD SUGAR SPIKE
It looks good.
-That cannot be bad.
-It's impossible.
Let me try the sweet potato mousse
left in the piping bag.
The sweet potato mousse.
This is Jonathan's favorite.
CURIOUS
Does the brûlée
taste like it can beat Sung-jun?
He did.
-He already did.
-Hey!
He did.
NAM-NO'S DIFFERENT TODAY!
THE OLDER TUBBY TWIN
GETS A HUGE COMPLIMENT
It tastes like sweet potato,
but it has another scent.
It's smooth and nice.
-He must be different today.
-They'd love it.
I can't wait to try it.
The time's 3 minutes and 20 seconds.
SUNG-JUN MAKES FRIED RICE
-Is that rice?
-He's beating on instant rice
to spread them out evenly.
-Fried eggs?
-Three minutes, twenty-one seconds.
He's making fried rice.
He's whipping up the fried rice.
His fried rice
doesn't look like Chinese cuisine,
but something that moms make at home.
Egg fried rice.
MEANWHILE, NAM-NO PLATES HIS FOOD
That looks so good.
KOUIGN-AMANN IS READY TOO
Looks good.
NAM-NO FINISHES FIRST
-Whoa!
-Nam-no's done.
A SUGAR-COATED DESSERT SET
CHECKING THE TIME
HE HAS 2 MINUTES AND 20 SECONDS
Now it's just Sung-jun.
Sung-jun's fried chicken.
Let me try a piece of fried chicken
with two minutes left.
Is it good enough to stop Nam-no
from winning a star for a long time?
Oh, no.
-Is it hot?
-It must be.
Swallow it.
It's been fried perfectly.
Really?
It tastes like orange.
And it's sweet.
Gosh.
FOUND THE INGREDIENT HE FORGOT
Can you pass me the kouign-amann?
The kouign-amann?
The kouign-amann is returning.
The bell got canceled.
The bell's canceled.
HEARS ABOUT THE CANCELLATION
-Canceled.
-Nam-no cancels his bell.
He canceled his bell.
SUNG-JUN HEARS IT AND CHECKS FOR TIME
FIXING UP THE SWEET POTATO-CHEESE CHOUX
-There's time.
-Yes.
Yes, Sung-jun may finish first.
Hurry up and ring the bell.
TOPPING THE KOUIGN-AMANN
RINGS THE BELL AGAIN
Nam-no finishes again.
JONATHAN'S FAVORITE TOAST SAUCE
-He's rubbing the sauce on it.
-What is this?
Wait, don't use too much!
-The sauce.
-Use more!
No, don't use too much.
-Use lots.
-Nam-no's finished.
COATED WITH THE SAUCE
He's coating the choux
with Jonathan's favorite sauce.
Just like that?
-Sugar.
-It's coated with sugar.
SUGAR-COATED S-C CHOUX
-It looks good.
-It does look good.
-Ten. Nine.
-Nine.
GREEN ONION
-Seven. Six.
-It looks good.
-Five.
-Four.
-He's good.
-Three.
CHILI PEPPER
-One.
-Are you done?
Sung-jun finishes as well.
A SWEET MEAL HAS BEEN MADE
Gosh, I can't even wait
for them to film inserts.
They already got a few shots.
SUGAR-FILLED DISHES ARE SERVED
That's insane.
All these sweet dishes
were made for the siblings.
Do you like it?
I don't just like it.
It's way more than I expected.
You can't seem to wait.
-Hurry up?
-I'm hungry. Yes.
Please try Chef Nam-no's
Beat Sung-jun Brûlée.
A DESSERT SET TO RECHARGE YOUR SUGAR LEVEL
BANANA CRÈME BRÛLÉE
MADE WITH LOTS OF SWEET POTATO MOUSSE
AND KOUIGN-AMANN,
EVEN LOOKING VISUALLY SWEET
WITH GRAPEFRUIT CHEONG
CHEF YOON NAM-NO'S BEAT SUNG-JUN BRÛLÉE
All right.
LET ME SERVE IT TO YOU
Sorry.
-You can just sit there.
-Sorry.
-I'm sorry about that.
-I'm sorry.
You aren't home right now.
You don't have to grab it first.
OLD HABITS DIE HARD
I need to wake up. It's a habit.
-She tries to grab it.
-I always have to be quick.
There are two pieces of bread,
and only one banana, right?
So she tried to grab the banana first.
-You should give way. In half, yes.
-Let's split it in half.
You're cutting it?
CAREFUL
-Excuse me. Can you hurry?
-Hurry up.
MEANWHILE, THESE SISTERS…
If they finish all those,
we can't get any, right?
They might make more later.
-What does she mean?
-Hurry up.
Will you hurry?
-She wants some leftovers.
-She wants that?
FIRST-COME, FIRST-SERVED
That's exactly
what you shouldn't be doing.
You take the bigger one.
That looks bigger.
-Use a spoon.
-Okay.
Do they eat the peel too?
PATRICIA TAKES THE FIRST BITE
JONATHAN TAKES A BITE TOO
Patricia took the first bite.
-She's suddenly praying.
-She's praying?
What is it, Jonathan?
HE ALSO PRAYS
What is it?
She's asleep.
I've missed this kind of flavor.
STRUCK BY THE BLOOD SUGAR SPIKE
Are you sleepy? The blood sugar spike?
-It's so delicious.
-It is?
You became wide-eyed.
And so suddenly.
-Are you sleepy?
-It's amazing!
MEANS IT 1,000%
Man. This thing.
One sec. Let me try it again.
He covered the top
with sweet potato mousse.
-Apple jam and yuja.
-Yuja and pear.
Apple jam, yuja, and pear.
YUM
I can taste everything.
When you watch an F1 race,
WHERE IS HE GOING WITH THIS?
…cars flash by so quickly.
LIKE THIS?
WHOOSH, ZOOM
Pear's flashing by,
and sweet potato is zooming right after.
They're all racing.
It's like a race in my mouth.
Nice metaphor.
-A race?
-It's good.
-So your mouth is the track?
-It's the track.
They're busy running on my teeth,
going up, down, forward, and zooming.
-It's an F1 race in his mouth.
-It's an F1 race.
-This is shocking.
-F1 race?
Who won?
-Currently, the first place…
-Who came in first?
Let me have one last bite.
One last bite. Swoosh.
-Start a race in there.
-Swoosh.
Swoosh. Sweet potato.
Sweet potato wins.
It's sweet potato.
CONGRATULATIONS
Also, the sugar on top.
The glazed sugar he made with that torch.
That's so crunchy.
It's a lot of fun.
IT SOUNDS GOOD
It's simply too good.
So that was the F1 race,
and there's one more.
-We'll try the next one.
-The next one.
You can each take one.
-You can take the bigger one.
-Okay.
-This one looks smaller.
-How sweet.
ARGH!
SPATTER
Ugh!
-It's okay.
-Did you drop it?
-I'm so curious.
-What's that?
-Kouign-amann.
-We're always making it the wrong way.
-The one Poong failed to make.
-That was reversed kouign-amann.
I must've started the trend
of making it wrong.
CRUNCH
-The sugar coating broke.
-It's crunchy to the touch.
CRUNCH
-It's coated with sugar and cereal.
-It looks good.
What is it?
What is it, Jonathan? What's wrong?
-Excuse me. Pull up your pants.
-Sorry.
IT'S MAKING ME FEEL UNPLEASANT…
-When you go to Haeundae…
-Haeundae?
-…people set off firecrackers.
-Firecrackers?
They're going off in my mouth.
They're crackling.
The one before zoomed by,
but this one pops up.
It keeps popping up.
First, it's this cereal.
You get it, right?
Will you talk?
Yes, tell the viewers about it.
THINKING OF WHAT TO SAY
The outside is really soft.
But the inside is really crispy.
-Isn't it the opposite?
-The outside is…
SOFT OUTSIDE, CRISPY INSIDE?
How can the inside be crunchy
while the outside is soft?
-It's been reversed.
-It's reversed.
It's another reversed kouign-amann?
That takes technique.
They had too much sugar,
-so they've become hyper.
-Yes.
-We have.
-They're in a frenzy.
It's really soft on the inside.
The inside is soft,
while this cereal on the outside
adds to the already crunchy dessert.
Crunchy outside, soft inside.
-Mmm.
-Did you use condensed milk?
-It's probably the butter.
-That's what makes it soft.
So butter was the one
-that gathered everyone.
-Gathered them?
-As one. It became one flavor.
-Yes.
-Butter is the centerpiece.
-What now?
-It's way too good.
-Wait.
-I've made my decision.
-Stop.
-Calm down.
-He makes quick decisions.
I'm sorry.
This must be grapefruit.
It is. And it's because
it has a bit of bitterness,
so I added that
to balance out the sweetness.
-He's a genius.
-Sweet and bitter.
-That's why you added it.
-NaKyoung.
-Really?
-She just said,
"He's a genius."
FOOD GENIUS
-I just pretend to be a fool.
-How did you manage
to fool everyone to this day?
You've fooled us all.
-He did.
-Yes.
I pretend to be stupid.
-The grapefruit…
-It's so good.
…is saying, "Calm down."
SWEETNESS, WHOA
"Don't be too sweet. That's too much."
"Pull back a little." Like that.
KOUIGN-AMANN: I'LL CALM DOWN…
-That was amazing.
-All right.
Next, Chef Sung-jun's dish,
It's Been O-range Since Nam-no Won a Star.
-O-range Since Nam-no Won a Star.
-O-range.
Take your time, Patricia.
Jong-won pulled the dish out,
and she began to devour
in case he took it all.
OH, RIGHT…
You aren't home, so you'll be fine.
You can't help it if you have siblings.
You have to eat quickly
when your mom's cleaning up.
It's so good.
-Was it good?
-Yes, thank you.
AMERICAN CHINESE-STYLE
ORANGE CHICKEN OVER RICE
AND SUGAR-COATED DESSERT,
SWEET POTATO-CHEESE CHOUX
CHEF KWON SUNG-JUN'S
IT'S BEEN O-RANGE SINCE NAM-NO WON A STAR
What should we begin with?
-Try the orange chicken with rice.
-The orange chicken.
He made fried chicken and rice.
You can have rice, chicken,
green onion, and pepper all at once.
Man.
Can't be bad!
-That just can't be bad.
-Exactly.
HAS TO BE GOOD
That looks great.
-It's a nice color.
-Jonathan.
The brother takes the first bite.
Fried chicken and rice.
THE SISTER TAKES A BITE TOO
CHUCKLE…
It's fun to watch him eat.
This is sweet
-in a whole new way.
-A new way?
-It's not a familiar taste?
-It's not.
The orange flavor
brings out the sweetness,
-but the fried rice balances it out.
-It does.
PRECISELY
You have to eat this together
to bring out all their potentials.
-This is delicious too.
-Back there,
I thought it was a bit too sweet.
-That's where the green onion comes in.
-That's true.
-It also tastes spicy.
-It does.
I balanced out the sweetness
with some chili pepper.
It balances it out.
-That sounds good.
-It sounds so good.
READY FOR ANOTHER BITE
-My gosh.
-Yes?
It looks so good.
Do you have some leftovers?
I do.
-I do.
-Yay.
-Aren't you full?
-You can finish yours.
LAST EPISODE
THE SIBLINGS SUFFERED
FROM WATCHING THE SISTERS
-This is hard.
-It is.
I didn't think it'd be this hard.
-It must've been tough for you.
-It's killing me.
That was last week,
so they're hungry again.
YUM
ALSO YUM
-Next up, sweet potato-cheese choux.
-This one.
-That looks nice.
-This one is just…
-It looks so pretty.
-It looks so good.
-It looks amazing.
-I'm excited.
Damyang, South Jeolla-do
is famous for donuts.
They left an impression on me.
-They're from that province.
-Yes.
-They live near Damyang.
-Yes, like Damyang donuts.
Damyang and Gwangju.
THE CROSS-SECTION LOOKS AWESOME
Man. Look at the cheese.
Yes, there's cheese inside too.
It's like sweet potato-cheese pork cutlet.
-Is it cheese and sweet potato mousse?
-Sweet potato mousse and cheese.
-And the toast sauce.
-He's had delicious donuts in Damyang.
WHAT WILL IT TASTE LIKE?
A HUGE BITE
It looks so soft.
PATRICIA'S FIRST BITE
-Is he asleep?
-He's asleep again.
-Blood sugar spike?
-Blood sugar spike.
-It's hitting him. He's asleep.
-Right away?
-Gosh.
-Is it good?
QUIETLY TAKES ANOTHER BITE
-That cream.
-It must be good.
-That looks so good.
-It's soft.
It looks so good.
TORMENTED
He's suddenly serious.
This is moving.
ALREADY MOVED
I bought that mousse
because I had a wish
to feel my mouth full of that mousse.
-A wish?
That was why I bought it.
The moment I took a bite,
the sweet potato
spread all around my mouth.
Then the cheese follows,
saying, "Wait up!"
And then the sugar crystals
slowly infiltrate my mouth one by one.
-This is like a party.
-I see.
-What party?
-What kind?
-Sugar. A sugar party.
-Sugar party.
It looked burnt. Does it taste burnt?
-Not at all.
-It wasn't burnt?
-It wasn't.
-I see.
It's even more delicious
because he chose to add cheese slices.
It balances out the sweetness.
Yes, that's sweet and salty.
-This is…
-It's so soft.
IN ONE BITE
Sung-jun put lots of work into that.
Patricia eats her choux very elegantly.
She's always been elegant.
Yes, that is the case.
We won't take it away,
so take your time to eat it.
-Thank you.
-Okay, then.
What about the sisters?
YAY
What a relief!
BURNING EYES
They've waited so long.
-Gosh.
-My gosh.
THEY FINALLY GET THE FOOD
-It looks great.
-It really does.
-I forgot to bring my phone.
-It looks nice.
I have mine.
It's in the shape of a banana,
but it's not made with it.
TOUCHES
HANDS OFF
She wants to take a picture first.
BIBI TAKES A BITE
She tries a bite.
NAKYOUNG TAKES A BITE TOO
Dishes by Chef Nam-no.
-It's an F1 race.
-It is?
I get what you mean. I get it.
She gets it.
"Sweet potato mousse."
"Pear."
That's so true.
I can taste the yuja too.
"Yuja."
"Banana."
The race must be quite close.
The sisters take a bite each.
That looks soft too.
It's an amusement park.
-An amusement park?
-Yes.
It's full of hopes and dreams.
You become very hopeful after you eat it.
That's why you mentioned firecrackers.
I'm suddenly becoming positive.
Eat it right before
you leave in the morning.
-It's waking me up.
-I see.
Is it too sweet for you two?
It is sweet,
but it tastes like happiness.
It skips the digestive system
and goes straight to your brain.
-Yes.
-The sugar, I mean. It's great.
BIBI takes the last bite.
She left a bite.
NAKYOUNG TAKES THE LAST BITE
Next, Chef Sung-jun's dish.
You've probably wondered.
A BIG BITE
He said it was a new kind of sweetness.
Does it have a great balance?
-Who made this?
-"Who made this?"
-Really?
-Yes, "Who made this?"
The sisters must love this one.
If this is American Chinese food,
I can settle in America.
I'm not sure
if this is Korean food or Chinese food.
It's confusing.
A confusing taste.
-It doesn't sound like a compliment.
-It doesn't?
It's positively confusing.
-How cute.
-It's confusing?
-All right. The decision.
-It's now time to decide.
Time to decide.
-I'm curious.
-Jonathan and Patricia.
Press one to choose Nam-no.
Press two to choose Sung-jun.
Make your decision and press a button.
UGH
Jonathan and Patricia.
ARGH!
-Are the siblings on the same page or not?
-What do we do?
We have the result.
Are Jonathan and Patricia
on the same page?
-They are.
-Hey!
It's two to zero.
-Emergency? Where's the light?
-He takes it during his round.
To stop us from using it against him.
-Emergency.
-Let's find out.
Yoon Nam-no versus Kwon Sung-jun,
who'll be the winner
between the look-alikes?
Let's find out the result.
So Sweet That It's to Die for.
Will it be Sung-jun or Nam-no?
-The ant or the anteater?
-The anteater?
-You're an anteater.
-Nam-no won all four rounds last year.
But Sung-jun won all two rounds this year.
Whose sweet dish
did Jonathan and Patricia like better?
-I can't watch this.
-Who won?
Who is it?
YOON NAM-NO WINS
Yoon Nam-no wins.
BEAT SUNG-JUN BRÛLÉE WINS
A BIG HUG
-Wait.
-The ant wins.
-I'm sleepy. I got sleepy while cooking.
-You did?
And we got that.
-Both dishes were excellent.
-Yes?
But which one was
So Sweet That It's to Die for?
What popped into my head was this.
THE F1 RACE
It was that sound.
"Pear."
-"Yuja."
-"Yoon Nam-no."
-"Sweetness."
-I see.
-I had no choice but to give it to him.
That banana's F1 race did the trick.
-That banana-shaped dessert.
-It was a shock.
This is Nam-no's first win
against Sung-jun this year.
So you are supposed
to cook with your tongue.
-He was right.
-Cook with your tongue.
-Must be disappointing, Sung-jun.
-He's surprised.
He surely is different, as a guy
who got into three digits through sweets.
You're going there?
You're mean.
He's mad.
-I'm going to lose weight too.
-All right.
Please put a star on Chef Nam-no!
-Good work.
-Congrats.
Nam-no finally wins a star.
-Congratulations, Nam-no!
-Congratulations.
A BIG HUG
This is Nam-no.
Let's take ten minutes off.
AFTER THE COOK-OFF
Do you have leftover rice?
LOOKING AROUND
It's all gone?
It's gone.
A BOLT OUT OF THE BLUE
REALLY? NOTHING?
Not even over there?
IN THE END, HE COULDN'T EAT ANYTHING
The second round of cook-off
with ingredients
from Jonathan and Patricia's fridge.
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong, here to show
the spiciness of the unorthodox,
versus Chef Sam Kim, here to show
the spiciness of his canine.
Sam's canine has been on a roll.
He's quite spicy.
During his cook-off with Chef Ho-young,
the freezer was out of power.
-What?
-Really?
I think the freezer's broken.
THE BINGO MANGSU INCIDENT
-Seriously. It's real.
-It's never happened before.
Bingo Mangsu.
It should've been a bingsu.
Well, we let it pass back then.
But last time,
when he went against Chef Sung-jun…
-Why is it off?
-What?
Who turned off the oven?
-The oven was off too.
-I'm getting chills.
This only happens to chefs
who go up against Sam.
Problems somehow arise.
-So our forensics team investigated.
-They did?
We'll have the results next episode.
There seemed to have been
canine marks on the electric wires.
-I knew it.
-It's becoming evident.
-There's a tooth mark?
-There are biting marks on the wire.
What's he hiding behind that kind smile?
We'll have the result soon.
These days,
even mice don't feed on electric wires.
No one ate it. It's just severed.
CAN'T ARGUE WITH THAT
Did you do that to win a star?
No, I really didn't.
After our viewers found out
about Sam's canine allegations,
-we had a tipster contact us.
-There was a tip?
There was proof
that he has done some things
using his canine before.
He had done it since his childhood.
WHO COULD IT BE?
He had once punctured holes
in his younger brother's sneakers
with his canine.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Only his family would know that.
-Explain this, please.
-He's a year younger, right?
-He is.
We often got into fights back then.
When sneakers with a layer of air
was trending,
I've punctured it once.
POPPING THE AIR
-You couldn't tell.
-With your canine?
A big hole would've been too obvious.
-Then it flattened slowly.
-With his canine?
So there's grounds for suspicion.
But after a few days,
my shoes began to flatten too.
Your brother wouldn't have let it pass.
We received another tip.
While Poong was getting ready
for his cook-off,
he saw a random screw.
Wait, where?
-Oh, my.
-I knew he'd do that.
I saw a random screw
near the microwave.
Something came off.
A MYSTERIOUS SCREW
WHO DID THIS?
It shouldn't have come off.
Did it have canine marks?
I plan to send it
to the National Forensic Service.
You've sent it to Forensics.
He asked
if I had a whetstone this morning,
and I thought he needed it for his knife.
Instead, he was sharpening
his canine in a corner.
SHARPENING
ADDITIONAL WITNESS ACCOUNTS
I knew it.
I saw lots of powder around.
It must've been him.
-It had to be him.
-Was this necessary?
I'm looking forward to seeing
what he has ruined today.
-Yes.
-And worried.
-I'm worried.
-Okay.
WEBTOON ARTIST KIM POONG'S INGREDIENTS:
CHEONGYANG PEPPER, BRISKET
CHEONGYANG PEPPER POWDER,
THIN PORK BELLY, OYSTER SAUCE
Poong, what are you making today?
I'll be using a lot of chili peppers.
The end-all dish of chili peppers.
-Chili peppers over rice.
-Chili peppers over rice?
First, I'll use
Cheongyang peppers
and fry them over high heat
to remove its skin.
Then it's left with the meat inside,
very soft yet extremely spicy.
I'll put that over rice.
Underneath the chili will sit
pork belly and brisket,
which will be boiled
and then mixed with spicy sauce.
To top it off,
I'll pour chili oil over the top.
-Three types of chili spiciness.
-That sounds spicy.
It's for "So Spicy That It's to Die for."
Someone might really go.
I have a feeling
that only one of them
will end up going home today.
One of us will leave on a stretcher,
the other will walk.
CHEF SAM'S INGREDIENTS:
CHEONGYANG PEPPER, CHUCK FLAP TAIL
CHEONGYANG PEPPER POWDER, BRISKET,
PORK BELLY, JJAMPPONG SAUCE, AND MORE
Sam's up against him today.
What are you making?
The name of my dish is
Deadly Hamburger.
SORRY?
-Deadly Hamburger.
-Deadly Hamburger. That's violent.
Whoa, I mean, listen to its name.
He's quite deadly today.
Who's going down?
It's not that I want to take anyone down.
I had to look through that dead fridge
to find enough ingredients for the burger.
OH, WE ALMOST MISUNDERSTOOD
-It was a misunderstanding.
-A wordplay.
WORDPLAY SAM
I'll prepare a hamburger meal.
He's making a hamburger meal.
First, a brisket salad.
Next, a burger.
Lastly, you had jjamppong soup base,
so I'll use that to make soup.
-You said you like it.
-I love it.
Will it go well with a hamburger?
-Hamburger with jjamppong soup?
-That's a new mix.
-One second.
-Like beef soup?
-It's odd.
-I don't see the vision.
You'll understand once you try it.
Okay. I'll look forward to it.
Let us begin their cook-off now.
Who knows who'll take it?
But Webtoon Artist Kim Poong is here
asking for an ambulance.
CHUCKLING
Chef Sam Kim has allegedly
made holes in sneakers and severed wires,
so today, he'll destroy Poong
with his canine.
Which one of them will survive?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
LET'S GO!
THIS TIME, A SPICY COOK-OFF!
Something spicy. Make it spicy.
How spicy can a hamburger be?
There's probably a limit.
He's probably making the patty first.
-Poong's chili oil.
-Poong's chili oil again.
Poong's chili oil.
-It's the base for all his dishes.
-The chili oil.
It's the famous oil.
APPROVED AS TRUE FANS
-Chili oil.
-Whoa.
He always begins by making chili oil.
It's so cool.
Sam's also making chili oil.
-What? Sam's chili oil.
-Sam's doing it too?
-Sam's chili oil.
-Is that the base?
Is that brisket?
-It is.
-Brisket.
Coat brisket with starch
and boil it in hot water,
and it becomes coated.
He's using that for the salad.
-I see.
-He's right.
-You're boiling it?
-Yes.
GARLIC!
IT SOUNDS PROFESSIONAL
ONE MORE TIME!
ROLLING
The garlic cloves are rolling away.
They're alive.
He doesn't seem professional,
but his dishes turn out well.
CHEONGYANG PEPPER POWDER!
-He's adding so much chili pepper.
-That looks too spicy.
He poured a bunch without looking.
He didn't even measure it.
GREEN ONION
1. POUR CHILI OIL
OVER MINCED GARLIC AND GREEN ONION
That looks nice.
It's still boiling hard.
-Is he making jjamppong?
-He is.
-It's like kimchi-jjigae.
-Is he making jjigae, stew?
Oyster sauce.
This much?
What are you making, Poong?
I'm making the seasoning
for pork belly and brisket.
I'll boil them first
and then mix them with this seasoning.
Seasoning.
-That's a lot of chili.
-That looks good.
Spiciness doesn't just come
from chili peppers. There's garlic too.
HE KNOWS WHAT'S UP!
-Garlic.
-It has to be a mix of chili and garlic.
You need that to…
Wait, this is an industry secret.
-An industry secret?
-Which industry?
Poong has an industry?
It must be the webtoon industry.
Words must be going around
in the webtoon industry.
-And onions are spicy too.
-He's adding onion too.
CHILI, GARLIC, ONION COLLAB
He's adding all the spicy veggies.
STRUGGLING
-What's wrong?
-That's right.
-What's with the machine?
-That's it.
The screw must've been from that blender!
That screw.
-Dang it.
-It's not working.
I knew it.
CHUCKLES
No, it wasn't me.
Wasn't it you?
I didn't do that.
-Sam must've unscrewed the blender.
-It wasn't me.
Don't let your guard down to the end.
Sam must be making the patty.
He blended pork belly and beef.
The patty has to be spicy
-for the burger to be spicy.
-True.
-The patty should be spicy.
-That's right.
Let's see what he'll use.
-Ground pepper.
Salt?
And he added a stash
of ground Cheongyang pepper.
I see, ground Cheongyang pepper.
He's adding a bit of spice into the patty.
-That's not a whole lot.
-That's not enough.
-It's not enough.
-It doesn't look spicy.
-You can add much more, Sam.
-It's already spicy.
-Add more.
-You can be bolder.
-Add everything.
I did.
Canine, you have no time to compromise.
ARE YOU FROM THE CANINE FAMILY?
Add more.
-Throw everything in.
-Throw it in.
3. MIX MEAT WITH CONDIMENTS AND PEPPER
He should add more Cheongyang pepper.
I hope he adds everything.
Is that bread?
-They're the buns.
-The buns.
Yes, for the burgers.
He said he'd fry and peel those,
then use only the inside.
Is that regular pepper? Not shishito.
-Shishito peppers?
-Cheongyang?
-Cheongyang, I think.
-Cheongyang peppers.
That's right.
SURPRISED
-It's splashing.
-Don't throw them in.
You're using lots of peppers.
He's frying so many of them.
-Sam.
-Yes?
Look at Poong.
He's using about three dozen peppers.
That must be one serving.
-They'll blow up.
-It's a pepper party.
-A pepper party.
Careful, Nam-no.
I think they'll blow up.
It smells spicy.
-They'll blow up.
-They're about to catch fire.
CHUCKLING
Was this why he wanted 911?
REQUESTING HELP
Right. They're slowly bubbling.
They're popping,
Pepper's popping.
3. FRY A BUNCH OF CHEONGYANG PEPPER
Poong's pepper's popping!
-Oh, no.
-They're blowing up too much.
-Aren't you going to peel them?
-Yes.
But wouldn't they be too hot?
-How will you do it?
-Careful.
-That looks way too spicy.
-I don't think you can do it.
It's been six minutes.
-What are they for, anyway?
-Topping for the rice.
-Wait, what's next?
-Peanut sauce.
-The patty.
-Peanut sauce. Yes.
PEANUT BUTTER, SOY SAUCE
VINEGAR
ONION, GREEN ONION
GROUND PEPPER, SAM'S CHILI OIL
RED PEPPER POWDER
SPICY BRISKET SALAD
Is the bread burnt?
-It's fine.
-It is?
HOW WILL HE MAKE THE BUNS SPICY?
-Are you putting peanut butter on them?
-Peanut butter.
Peanut butter will make it delicious.
But not spicy.
You should be using gochujang!
That'll kill the spiciness.
-This is the spiciness round.
-Add more red pepper powder.
-Is he grilling the patty?
-The patty.
You should add more pepper.
Look at how much pepper
Poong is using over there.
He won't even listen.
I can't even see any green on it.
No, but Sam's taking his own journey.
What is that journey?
I have no idea.
6. BOIL GARLIC, JJAMPPONG SAUCE,
AND BRISKET BROTH
Seven minutes? I need to warm up the rice.
-Brisket.
-Brisket and thin pork belly.
INSTANT RICE, INTO THE MICROWAVE
7 MINUTES?
Sam's grilling three Cheongyang peppers.
-Poong's using 30, he's using 3.
-Did you say 30?
-Thirty is way too much, isn't it?
-Ten times as much.
The difference is tenfold.
There's no middle ground.
THAT FACE
I love it when he makes that face.
He's scared that the peppers will pop.
IT MEANS HE'S DONE FRYING
It's tough for him too.
He's not even breathing.
He's not? It must be spicy.
BREATHING
A HUGE QUANTITY
I'll grind this one more time.
I'll work on you first.
-Wait, Poong. Set it to six.
-How?
This is too weak. Try this.
Whoa!
Is it working?
Why was the setting on low?
I remember setting it up before.
-It was set on low?
-It's really weird.
-He drops the seasoning.
-That looks really spicy.
That's way too much.
There's more seasoning than meat.
CHEONGYANG PEPPER POWDER!
-Cheongyang pepper powder!
-That's…
-Cheongyang powder.
-It's Cheongyang pepper powder.
5. MIX MEAT WITH SEASONING
AND PEPPER POWDER
I have work tomorrow!
He won't be able to wake up.
You have work tomorrow?
You wanted spicy food.
Well, that's great.
But I might have to stay home.
A RECIPE THAT KEEPS YOU HOME
Sam, what's that soup? Is it a stew?
-It's probably jjamppong.
-It's jjamppong?
He should be throwing in spicy chili,
but he's adding green onion instead.
Why are you using so much green onion?
-Use some spicy chili.
-Add more chili.
What's Sam doing now? There he goes!
-He poured that in.
-Add more!
This is really spicy.
It'll take a while to peel the peppers.
-It must be hot.
-It'll take up about five minutes.
Can you do that alone?
I doubt it. It's hot!
AN EXTREME MISSION
-Do you need help?
-I'll put on some gloves.
-Five minutes.
-Five minutes left.
Jung-hwan, please go
and try some of the dishes.
It smells spicy.
-Whoa. The air.
-Please go check.
-I can smell it now.
-It's in the air.
Can you peel these? Thanks.
Say, "Please help me."
Help! Please help me, good sir!
-Please help me!
-The peppers.
You'd better peel them quickly.
-It takes a while.
-He can't do anything else.
IT'S SO HOT
I give up. It's too hot.
-Hurry up.
-I can't help it. Let's go.
-Let's go.
-It's hot.
6. PEEL FRIED CHEONGYANG PEPPERS
-I'm so sorry, Poong.
-No, Nam-no! You have to do it!
-I need help!
-Give me those. I got it.
What's going on?
There are too many people
working on this dish.
DID YOU SEE HIS FACE?
ENRAGED
I could've done the same.
Everyone, come and help!
PULLING UP
This jjamppong soup looks spicy.
The soup, Jung-hwan.
Sam told me to try the soup first.
The soup.
He can't try it, so he's making me.
-The soup.
What's the soup like?
Is it deadly?
-Far from it.
-He needs more.
If it's not spicy to him,
it probably isn't.
-Avocado?
-I can't eat spicy food, either.
It kills the spiciness.
That'll cancel it out.
-Do I need to add more?
-It has to be much spicier.
-Just pour it in. More.
-More.
That jjamppong soup looks really spicy.
-It's hot.
-The peppers are still under way.
It's way too hot.
The peppers are too hot
for them to be peeled quickly.
Hot peppers.
Why don't you try a hot pepper?
-This hot pepper? Me?
-Jung-hwan.
-"Me?"
-Try it.
Well, I shall try it
if I must do it for the show.
-See how spicy it is.
-That's way too big.
Have it in a bite.
In one bite.
Spicy-Chili, Spicy Spicy-Chili?
HOW SPICY IS IT?
WHERE IS HE GOING?
UNABLE TO SWALLOW
It's extremely spicy!
-It must be really spicy.
-I told you.
-I need water.
He made 30 of those?
-You'd die.
-That's insane.
-I have work tomorrow!
-I'm curious.
You wanted spicy food!
-He was determined to make it spicy.
-I have work tomorrow.
That's bad news.
-Jung-hwan will die first.
-If Sam doesn't make it spicier,
-…he'll lose 100%.
-Sam?
-No, it's spicy.
-It is?
CHEESE?
ADDING CHEESE
SPICINESS, DOWN
GRILLED CHEONGYANG PEPPERS
SPICINESS, UP
SRIRACHA
MAYONNAISE
SPICINESS, DOWN
7. MIX SRIRACHA, MAYO,
GROUND CHEONGYANG PEPPER TO MAKE SAUCE
GRILLED CHEONGYANG PEPPER
ASSEMBLING THE SPICY HAMBURGER
He's putting avocado inside.
Hamburger with avocado.
-It must be for Patricia.
-You can use avocado like that?
-He's assembling it.
-It looks good.
Yes, it does look good.
SPICY, OH SO SPICY HAMBURGER
It's still spicy!
A minute and 30 seconds.
Why am I filming myself?
Time's passing.
Peppers over rice.
-Meat goes over the rice.
-This should be enough.
-He's putting the meat on top.
-Okay.
Jonathan, if you finish this,
-you get my approval.
-Is this enough?
You'd be the best
when it comes to spicy food.
-The best?
-The best with spicy food.
-He snacks on Cheongyang peppers.
-It's going on top of the meat.
-That's true.
-Yes?
But that'd kill me.
YOUR CRIME IS ASKING
THE COOK OF THE DARKNESS FOR SPICY FOOD
It's too true to the order.
That looks more deadly.
Poong!
-It's not just deadly.
-You asked me for spicy food.
-You're already dead.
-Dead.
Fifty seconds left.
-Now, you still have time.
-Wait, that looks so spicy.
-The air in here is already spicy.
-Yes.
-Thirty seconds.
-You have enough time.
Thirty seconds.
-Sam finishes first.
-Great job!
He finished first.
Poong's dish is topped with his chili oil.
FAREWELL, JONATHAN…
My stomach is starting to hurt.
I have work tomorrow.
Ten seconds left.
-Sesame oil.
-Yes.
-Nine.
-More?
Eight.
Seven.
-Six.
-Five.
-Four.
-Three.
-Two.
-One.
KIM POONG FINISHES
SPICY-CHILI, SPICY SPICY CHILI
-That looks good.
-Poong's done.
-I can feel it.
-It's spicy.
The air's really spicy.
You'll have to take tomorrow off.
A THERAPEUTIC DISH FOR A DAY OFF
I have to go home today.
Jung-hwan jumped up and down.
This is bad.
SO WHO'LL TAKE THE AMBULANCE?
-I'm curious.
-All dishes are finished.
Hey.
Don't eat that.
-Why not?
-You'll be in trouble.
Both dishes were finished
for the siblings.
WOW
-Your response made it seem dangerous.
-It's crazy.
It's not the kind
-of chili pepper for humans.
-No?
Do I still have my tooth here?
I can't feel anything.
Am I missing a tooth?
-Was it that spicy?
-It's driving me nuts.
They were to make spicy dishes,
but spiciness alone can't win this round.
-Right. It has to be good.
-Yes, that's right.
Sam Kim's dishes are up first.
Deadly Hamburger.
SPICY BRISKET SALAD
AND CHEONGYANG PEPPER PATTY BURGER
SERVED WITH SPICY JJAMPPONG SOUP
CHEF SAM KIM'S DEADLY HAMBURGER
-Try that first. The jjamppong soup.
-It's here.
It's so spicy.
What do they begin with?
-First, that salad.
-Salad.
We'll try the salad first.
You can take some.
You're saying that because it's salad.
CHUCKLE…
ALREADY BICKERING BEFORE THEY EAT
You let her go first,
but she still complains.
-He's being nice, but I still complain.
-You did.
There's nothing I can eat today.
-Right. You don't look well.
-I'm sad.
You've lost some weight.
GAUNT?
What's the salad made of?
Green onion, onion, brisket,
-and chili oil.
-It looks spicy too.
It's not the kind of salad I expected.
It's been Koreanized. Looks great.
They take a bite together.
It looks good.
-Mmm.
-What is it?
This needs rice.
Like a side dish.
I can finish a bowl of rice easily
with this salad.
-Whoa.
-Before I start the main dish.
I can finish a bowl easily.
This sauce is fantastic.
THIS ONE'S GOOD
So he made a burger instead of rice.
-Yes.
-To eat it with the salad.
-It makes me crave more food.
-Crave?
-This was a big success.
-He wants more food.
-Yes.
-How spicy is it?
-Not at all.
-Not spicy at all.
-This wasn't deadly.
-This one wasn't.
It'll continue to get spicier.
It was Deadly Hamburger, not Deadly Salad.
-Not Deadly Salad? Sorry.
-It was the hamburger.
THE SPICY SALAD
WASN'T SPICY ENOUGH FOR THEM
Jonathan had almost fainted
after eating the Deadly Pork Cutlet.
Deadly Hamburger.
If it's not spicy, your senses are broken.
He's eating it in one bite.
He eats so well.
YUM
And the avocado.
-The patty's made with lots of pepper.
-Is it spicy?
-It should be.
-I'm sure it is.
HOW SPICY IS THE HAMBURGER?
-I don't think it is.
-It doesn't look it.
-It's not spicy at all.
-Emergency. Not at all?
-Not at all.
-It's not spicy at all.
He couldn't forget his ethics.
It doesn't even have a hint of spiciness.
The avocado adds a really nice flavor,
but that's what kills
whatever bit of spiciness it had.
-It's gone?
-It killed it.
We told you to add more.
This isn't spicy?
He added Cheongyang pepper
to the patty, so how about that?
It just adds a nice texture.
-Only the texture?
-In terms of spiciness,
it's not spicy at all.
But the dish itself is fantastic.
-I see.
-It's not spicy at all.
-It's an emergency.
-Wait.
Could the last one be the spiciest?
WE KNEW JJAMPPONG WOULD BE SPICY
I hope it's hot.
JJAMPPONG, YOU♥
THEN WE'LL BE SATISFIED
It wasn't supposed to be called
Deadly Hamburger.
It was Deadly Jjamppong.
-I see. Right.
-That's the original name.
-The jjamppong.
-That's Deadly Jjamppong.
Here we go.
I hope it's spicy.
SMACKING LIPS
UNSURE
-They're too good with spicy food.
-He grabs some meat.
-It's crimson red.
-It looks so spicy.
-Meat and green onion.
-Their senses are broken.
He added lots of Cheongyang powder.
BREATHING…
It still looks steaming hot.
IT'S HOT
THE JJAMPPONG WAS STILL PIPING HOT
Is it deadly because of the temperature?
I was surprised.
I almost lost my tongue.
This reminded me
of the fried rice
served with orange chicken.
If I brought that
and mixed it with this soup,
I would've died.
THE SOUP THAT CALLS FOR RICE
It tastes like really good jjamppong.
But then it's also like jjigae,
somewhere in-between.
It's so good. The meat is tender too.
Is it spicy?
It's not spicy.
BUT HE ADDED
SO MUCH CHEONGYANG PEPPER POWDER…
-It tastes like rich yukgaejang.
-Yes!
-But it's not spicy?
-It's not spicy.
Is something wrong with us?
Go see a doctor.
See a doctor.
But it's delicious.
-It's just delicious jjamppong?
-Yes.
-He tried his best.
-But it's not too spicy.
-It's all right.
-It's too hot.
IS THE SPICINESS HITTING HER LATER?
-It is?
OH…
But it's not spicy.
When it's hot, it feels spicier.
These two dishes
would go so well with rice.
Right out of the cooker.
The kind when you get a piece on your hand
while scooping, you go, "Ouch."
CAN CONNECT
That's so real. You go, "Ouch."
It would've been great with rice.
I want to try that.
You know, he's looking at us
like he's saying, "Just wait."
It's kind of scary.
-Spicy-Chili, Spicy Spicy-Chili.
-It's like that.
Please try Spicy-Chili, Spicy Spicy-Chili.
HERE TO PRESENT THE KIND OF SPICINESS
WAY OVER THE LINE
ONLY THE MEAT OF FRIED CHEONGYANG PEPPERS
WEBTOON ARTIST KIM POONG'S
SPICY-CHILI, SPICY SPICY-CHILI
Jung-hwan jumped after trying his dish.
How will they receive it?
I'll try the pepper first.
I was getting curious.
-We'll taste it and see what it's like.
-Sure.
-See if Jung-hwan's response is justified.
First, they try just the chili peppers.
-They love spicy food.
-Will they find it spicy?
I don't think so.
-They're good with spicy food.
-It's spicy.
SAVORING CAREFULLY
-Jung-hwan had jumped up and down.
-It was so spicy for me.
-We should start acting.
-It's us.
-We should go, "It's spicy!"
-Right?
-Are you serious?
-That's too fake.
I'm sorry, but it's not that bad.
CLICK
-That was really spicy.
-Will it hit me later?
WHAT ON EARTH IS GOING ON?
What's that green and long vegetable?
-Okra?
-Okra!
They feel like okra.
-What?
-It's that mild?
It's that weak?
Okra?
-Okras aren't spicy.
-They aren't.
Is something wrong with me?
Or are they weird?
Now, let us dig in.
I love how he gave us so much meat.
-Yes.
-I love it.
-So this isn't spicy for you?
-But it is.
He's eating three at once.
A MOUTH FULL OF CHILI PEPPERS
-It must be spicy for Patricia.
-It's spicy.
It's still hot.
OH DEAR GOODNESS
I think they feel spiciness
only in the temperature.
-They don't have pain receptors.
-Jonathan.
FINDS THEM FASCINATING
It tastes like a delicious bowl
-of jeyuk-bokkeum over rice.
-Jeyuk-bokkeum over rice?
-But it's topped with okra.
-Okra.
It's okra and spicy pork?
IN SHOCK
-That's insane.
-It's okay.
It tastes like jeyuk-bokkeum
with lots of green onion.
Is it sweet?
That much green onion would've been spicy.
-Pork and green onion.
-They're in an emergency.
-They've lost their taste buds.
-They can only taste sweetness.
You aren't even sweating.
We would be if it was spicy,
but we're not.
-I'm curious.
-Me too.
Should the spicy sisters try it?
I'm dying to know.
-It really isn't spicy?
-No, I guess it should've been.
Your breath smells really spicy.
-Thank you.
-His jjamppong soup was the spiciest.
-Do you want it?
-Yes, I'm curious.
I haven't had anything today.
I'M HUNGRY
Try the jjamppong soup first.
THEY TRY JUST THE JJAMPPONG TOGETHER
-It's good.
-It just tastes pleasantly spicy.
And it's thick.
-So it's not too spicy?
-Just pleasantly spicy.
-I want some rice.
-Don't you?
White rice.
-This isn't spicy.
-So it's not too spicy.
COUGH
It must be spicy.
Did you eat a pepper?
Oh, no.
GOT ATTACKED WHILE EATING
What the heck?
Almost threw her fan at him.
OH, NAM-NO…
-I'm hearing a water deer.
-Water deer?
IT MUST'VE BEEN SO SPICY…
-A water deer?
-He sounds like one.
THE WATER DEER RETURNS
-He thought it'd pass.
-I'm sorry. Isn't it spicy?
SO THE JJAMPPONG SOUP WAS SPICY
Please try Poong's dish.
Spicy-Chili, Spicy Spicy-Chili.
She tries a whole pepper.
See how spicy it is.
The siblings are way too…
What's it like?
Is it deliciously spicy?
Chefs, please try it. Chef Eun-yeong.
It's too spicy.
-It's hitting them. It hits Nam-no.
-It's too spicy.
-It's spicy.
-Is it?
Don't eat it, then.
Why do you torture yourself?
But I'm hungry.
So it is spicy.
It must be spicy for her too.
WHAT'S IT LIKE FOR BIBI?
What's it like?
NATURALLY GOING FOR THE SOUP
-See?
-You're cooling off with that?
USING SAM'S SOUP
TO QUENCH POONG'S SPICINESS
She uses Sam's soup
to cool off Poong's dish.
-See? Mine's spicy.
-That's hilarious.
The spiciness lingers.
It stays.
DASHING TO HER FRIDGE
It hits BIBI later.
-Please try it, Sung-ju.
-What?
I've had it.
-You have to eat the pepper.
-It's really spicy.
It's the pepper.
Just the pepper?
At least let me have the rice too.
-Try this first.
-Give me the rice too.
Let me feed it to you.
THE SISTERS CALM DOWN WITH MILK
Just stay still.
I've tried it already.
It's like a punishment.
I'll try it.
-You have to try it.
-He's done.
STOPS HERE
Ugh.
COULDN'T STAND IT AND SPITS IT OUT
It's already spicy.
-Already.
-Eat it.
Stop lying.
-But it is.
-Just eat it.
Eat it already. I've had it too.
HEHEHE…
Don't give me that look.
Eat it.
This is insane.
-Open up.
-It's not that bad.
-It's not spicy.
-It's not too spicy.
It is.
Man.
Gosh.
TEARY-EYED
My stomach hurts.
I want ice cream.
-It's spicy.
-Take some.
Can you get me one too?
-And me.
-It's too spicy.
DASHING
What's with the boys?
I found something.
Do you want dark chocolate?
GETS CHOCOLATE
It's cold.
-This is such a relief.
-That's much better.
-What do you think, Eun-yeong?
-Me?
I'm not so bad with spicy food,
but I think I can win a fight
with my sister after eating this.
HER SPIRIT IS ON FIRE
-It makes me mad.
-Mad?
It's too spicy for ordinary people,
but it must've been fine for you two.
-Yes.
-So neither dish was spicy?
As you can see,
-nothing is going on with me.
-My tummy hurts.
-They should be on Believe It or Not.
-Believe It or Not?
That was insane.
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH
Press one for Sam,
two for Poong.
Make your decision and press the button.
UNSURE
-Okay.
-I'm done.
We have the result.
Jonathan and Patricia chose
-the same person.
-Wait, what?
They truly are siblings.
-That's crazy.
-You two are close.
Why did you bicker so much?
Hold hands from now on.
-No way.
GO?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
Which one did they choose?
Let's see the result. Show us.
So Spicy That It's to Die for.
Which one did they choose?
Will Poong show
his strong side against Sam?
Or will Sam beat Poong
and tie him at nine stars?
Which side was it, Jonathan and Patricia?
Who's the winner?
KIM POONG WINS
SPICY-CHILI, SPICY SPICY CHILI WINS
Poong wins this round.
He's very strong against Sam this year.
Both dishes were good,
but I like rice with toppings.
Also the peppers on top
weren't extremely spicy,
but it still had a bit of spice.
-Yes.
-So that's why.
Was Sam's dish
just an ordinary meal?
A very delicious yet ordinary meal.
-It was delicious.
-And mild.
-It was mild and delicious.
-Like gukbap.
Poong now moves into two digits.
He's now alone in second place
with ten stars.
ALONE IN 2ND PLACE, KIM POONG
Please put a star on him.
Great job.
He takes his tenth victory
with that spicy dish! Sam…
No, Poong.
BROKEN
Oh, no.
Congratulations, Poong.
COMING UP: THE PREVIEW
Today's fridge owner!
THIS IS HUGE
WOOHOO!
Hello.
I'm Son Ye-jin.
-You're everyone's first love.
-I can't look at her. She's too pretty.
COPYING YE-JIN'S HAIRSTYLE
She's one of Korea's best actors.
AN ACTING CHALLENGE?
Have you eaten?
-The angry version.
-You've eaten?
Have you eaten?
HEART DROPS
Even the elderly have feelings.
-We present Ye-jin's fridge!
-Fridge!
What's this?
My husband got it as a gift,
and it's apparently quite valuable.
So I brought it in secret.
-So many dishes.
-Your kid eats it too?
My kid devours side dishes
and even drinks the soup.
It looks so good.
Let's look through every single one.
This is really good.
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin
for Son Ye-jin!
THE TALENTED CHEFS
COMPETE TO CAPTURE HER TASTE
You said you liked a bit of texture.
This is my care and devotion.
LOVING IT
A 2:2 TEAM DEATH MATCH
CHINESE SISTERS
VS. WESTERN MASTER-DISCIPLE
Turn on the heat at 11 minutes.
THE CHINESE SISTERS CAME READY
Can Western cuisine do that?
WE CAN DO THIS INSTEAD
I'll let you jump on my wagon,
so just follow my instructions.
-I'll do it.
-I got it.
OKAY!
-Should I go on?
-Grind it now.
ONLY FOLLOWING THE INSTRUCTIONS
It smells so good.
SHE EATS WELL
Mmm.
It must be good.
WHICH DISH WILL MAKE HER PLEASED?
Have you eaten?
Chef Eun-yeong, have you taken your meds?
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn